Guide to the Lewis Zurlo Associates Architecture & Interior Design Collection MS 028
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series 1: Job Files, 47217
  - 97-08: Savings Bank of Danbury, Loan Center, 1997-2000, 47368
    - Test Reports, 1997-2000; 47379 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Letters & Memos, 1997-2000; 47378 (Box 8, Folder 32-35)
    - Requests for Messages and Information, 1997-2000; 47377 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Transmittals, 1997-2000; 47376 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Roofing, 1997-2000; 47375 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Contemplated Change Orders, 1997-2000; 47374 (Box 8, Folder 39-45)
    - Shop Drawing Log, 1997-2000; 47373 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Architectural (1-17), 1997-2000; 47372 (Box 8, Folder 47-61)
    - Structural, 1997-2000; 47371 (Box 9, Folder 1-7)
    - Mechanical & Electrical, 1997-2000; 47370 (Box 9, Folder 8-14)
    - Job Files, 1997-2000; 47369 (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
  - 97-09 - 97-16, 49840
    - 97-09: Coach Tours, 1997; 47367 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - 97-10: Green Renovation, 1997; 47366 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - 97-11: Tarrywile Lavatories, 1997; 47365 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - 97-12: Colangelo Car Wash, 1998-1999; 47364 (Box 9, Folder 20-21)
    - 97-13: Cordeiro Apartment, 1997; 47363 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - 97-14: Datahr III, 1997; 47362 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - 97-15: Bigelow Addition, 1997; 47361 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - 97-16: 264 Main Street, 1997; 47360 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - 97-17: Palace View Senior Housing, 1997-1999, 47347
    - Palace View Senior Housing, 1997-1999; 47359 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Inspections, 1997-1999; 47358 (Box 9, Folder 31-33)
    - Certificates for Payment, 1997-1999; 47357 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Sketches, Measurements & Clarifications, 1997-1999; 47356 (Box 9, Folder 35-37)
    - Letters & Memos, 1997-1999; 47355 (Box 9, Folder 38-39)
    - Requests for Information, 1997-1999; 47354 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Test Reports Transmittals, 1997-1999; 47353 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Shop Drawing Log, 1997-1999; 47352 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Architectural (1-10), 1997-1999; 47351 (Box 9, Folder 43-45)
    - Structural (1-3), 1997-1999; 47350 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Mechanical (1-6), 1997-1999; 47349 (Box 9, Folder 47-52)
    - Job Files, 1998-1999; 47348 (Box 9, Folder 53-55)
  - 97-19: Danbury Community Health Center, 1991-1999, 47327
    - Phase I & Phase II Environmental Study, 1991; 47346 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
    - Job Files, 1991-1999; 47345 (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
    - Community Health Center (9752), 1991-1999; 47344 (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
    - Community Health Center (9752) Millwork and Casework Manual, 1991-1999; 47343 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
    - Community Health Center (9752) Millwork and Casework Drawings, 1991-1999; 47342 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
    - Notes, 1997-1998; 47341 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Certificates for Payment & Change Orders, 1991-1999; 47340 (Box 10, Folder 9-13)
    - Letters, Memos and Clippings, 1991-1999; 47339 (Box 10, Folder 14-15)
    - Addendums, Sketches, Clarifications, Bids, 1991-1999; 47338 (Box 10, Folder 16-18)
    - Requests for Information, 1991-1999; 47337 (Box 10, Folder 19-20)
    - Test Reports/Transmittals, 1991-1999; 47336 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Equipment, 1991-1999; 47335 (Box 10, Folder 22-23)
    - Shop Drawing Log, 1991-1999; 47334 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Architectural (1-13), 1991-1999; 47333 (Box 10, Folder 25-36)
    - Mechanical (1-8), 1991-1999; 47332 (Box 10, Folder 37-48)
    - Structural (1-6), 1991-1999; 47331 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Plan (9752), 1991-1999; 47330 (Box 10, Folder 50-51)
    - Proposal, Caldwell & Walsh, 1991-1999; 47329 (Box 10, Folder 52-53)
    - Danbury Community Health Center and Senior Meeting Hall, Project Directory, 1991-1999; 47328 (Box 10, Folder 54-56)
  - 98-11, 98-41, 49841
    - 98-11: Union Savings Bank, Loan Servicing Center, 1998; 47326 (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
    - 98-41: National Ceramic Products, 1998; 47325 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 98-62: Women's Center of Greater Danbury, Phase I, II, III & IV, 1998-2002, 47317
    - Specifications (0212), 1998-2002; 47324 (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
    - Phase III: Letters, Memos, Photos, 1998-2002; 47323 (Box 11, Folder 7-11)
    - Phase III: Shop Drawings (0212), 1998-2002; 47322 (Box 11, Folder 12-14)
    - Phase IV: Certif. for Payments & Change Orders, 1998-2002; 47321 (Box 11, Folder 15-17)
    - Phase IV: Agreements, 1998-2002; 47320 (Box 11, Folder 18-21)
    - 2nd Floor H. C. Bathrooms Only (2015), 1998-2002; 47319 (Box 11, Folder 22-26)
    - Shop Drawings, 1998-2002; 47318 (Box 11, Folder 27-32)
  - 98-64 - 99-29, 49842
    - 98-64: Harrison Square II, 1998; 47316 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - 99-12: Division Street Plumbing, 1999; 47315 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - 99-17: Samuelson Property, 1999; 47314 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - 99-21: Durkin, Inc., 1999; 47313 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - 99-21: Durkin Awnings Building, 1999; 47312 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - 99-29: Club 2000 (See 04-01), 1999; 47311 (Box 11, Folder *)
  - 99-40: Savings Bank Changes, 2000, 47308
    - Savings Bank Changes, 2000; 47310 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Generator, Diebold Equip., Drapery, 4th Floor, Furniture, Extra Signs, 1998-2000; 47309 (Box 11, Folder 39-44)
  - 99-42: Harrison Square II, 1999-2001, 47287
    - Harrison Square II (99-49?), 1999-2001; 47307 (Box 11, Folder 45-55)
    - Letters & Memos, 1999-2001; 47306 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
    - Sketches, 1999-2001; 47305 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - 99-43: BRT General Corp., Tenant #1, 1999; 47304 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - 99-45: Flagship Communications, 1999; 47303 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - 99-48: CBG Offices, Ryer Associates/Ryer Apartments, 1999-2001; 47302 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 99-52: Coffee Please, 1999; 47301 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - 99-53: Santos Bakery Project, 1999; 47300 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - 99-54: Budis Assisted Living, 1999; 47299 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - 99-60: Holiday Inn Convenience Court, 1999; 47298 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - 20-03: Danbury Medical Group, 2000; 47297 (Box 12, Folder 12-13)
    - 20-06: The Empress Ballroom, 2000; 47296 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - 20-10: Sure Power Corp. Interior, 2000; 47295 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - 20-13: Leahy's Showroom, 2000; 47294 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - 20-16: Visual Intelligence Agency, 2000; 47293 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - 20-18: Friedman Renovation, 2000; 47292 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - 20-20: Sounds Incredible Addition, 2000-2001; 47291 (Box 12, Folder 19-20)
    - 20-22: Sounds Incredible II, 2000; 47290 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - 20-23: Fairpoint Communications, 2000; 47289 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - 20-27: Housatonic Tourism, 2000; 47288 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - 20-28: Zotos Town Houses, 2000-2005, 47273
    - Zotos Town Houses, 2000-2005; 47286 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Proposals, Prices, Bids, 2000-2005; 47285 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Letters, Fax, Notes, 2000-2005; 47284 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Specification Cuts, 2000-2005; 47283 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Sketches, 2000-2005; 47282 (Box 12, Folder 28-31)
    - 20-30: Risk Night Club Restaurant, 2000; 47281 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - 20-31: City Sports Café, 2000; 47280 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - 20-32: Augustano Homes Repair, 2000-2001; 47279 (Box 12, Folder 34-42)
    - 20-32: Augustano Homes (most recent), 2000-2002; 47278 (Box 12, Folder 43-46)
    - 20-37: Montessori School, 2000; 47277 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - 20-40: Bisbano Addition, 2000-2001; 47276 (Box 12, Folder 48-50)
    - 20-43: Concession Stand Addition (Rogers Park), 2000-2001; 47275 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - 20-44: Scientech Case Study, 2000-2001; 47274 (Box 12, Folder 52-53)
  - 20-45: Paulo's Auto Repair (0145 & 0204), 2001-2005, 47268
    - Paulo's Auto Repair, 2001-2005; 47272 (Box 12, Folder 54-55)
    - Letters & Memos, 2001-2005; 47271 (Box 12, Folder 56-57)
    - Certificates for Payment & Change Orders, 2001-2005; 47270 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Shop Drawings, 2001-2005; 47269 (Box 12, Folder 59-61)
  - 20-47 - 01-60, 49843
    - 20-47: Christian Science Church, 2000-2001; 47267 (Box 12, Folder 62-63)
    - 20-50: Leili Apartments, 2000-2002; 47266 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Unknown Job Number: Bernadino's, 1999-2001; 47265 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - 20-51: Duncan Apartments (0206), 2001-2004; 47264 (Box 12, Folder 66-69)
    - Unknown Job Number: DaSilva Proposal 197 Main Street, 2000; 47263 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - 20-56: Savings Bank Mezzanine, 1999-2001; 47262 (Box 13, Folder 1-4)
    - 01-02: Burton's Bridge, 2000-2005; 47261 (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
    - 01-05: Radial Bearing Offices, 2001; 47260 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 01-25: Buzaid Apartment, 2001; 47259 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - 01-37: Galleria Commercial Loan Center, undated; 47258 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 01-39: 12 Crosby Street, 2001; 47257 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - 01-41: Surveys Nationwide, 2001; 47256 (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
    - 01-46: Mysore Addition (0206), 2001; 47255 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - 01-50: Leili Apartments, 2001; 47254 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - 01-60: Radial Bearings Office, 2001; 47253 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 02-02: Senior Center (Elmwood Hall), 2001-2003, 47232
    - Senior Center (Elmwood Hall), 2001-2003; 47252 (Box 13, Folder 16-18)
    - Shop Drawing Log, 2001-2003; 47251 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Shop Drawing Log: Architectural, 2001-2003; 47250 (Box 13, Folder 20-35)
    - Shop Drawing Log: Structural, 2001-2003; 47249 (Box 13, Folder 36-41)
    - Shop Drawing Log: Mechanical & Electrical, 2001-2003; 47248 (Box 13, Folder 42-52)
    - Reference Drawing: E-1, 2001-2003; 47247 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
    - Job Files, 2002-2004; 47246 (Box 13, Folder 53-54)
    - Meetings/Memos/Letters, 2001-2003; 47245 (Box 13, Folder 55-57)
    - Sketches, 2001-2003; 47244 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - Cert. for Payments and Change Orders, 2001-2003; 47243 (Box 14, Folder 3-8)
    - Request for Information, 2001-2003; 47242 (Box 14, Folder 9-12)
    - Job Files, 2001-2002; 47241 (Box 14, Folder 13-22)
    - Meeting Minutes, 2001-2003; 47240 (Box 14, Folder 23-31)
    - Bids, 2001-2003; 47239 (Box 14, Folder 32-38)
    - Job Files, 2000-2002; 47238 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Specifications, 2001-2003; 47237 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Letters/Memos/Meetings, 2001-2003; 47236 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Code Information, 2001-2003; 47235 (Box 14, Folder 42-43)
    - Sketches, 2001-2003; 47234 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Contracts, 2001-2003; 47233 (Box 14, Folder 45-48)
  - 02-04 - 04-06, 49844
    - 02-04: Eleven Ives Street, 2002; 47231 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - 02-05: Blackstone Industries, 2002; 47230 (Box 14, Folder 50-51)
    - 03-02: House Study #1 (Zimmerman) 1992, 2003; 47229 (Box 14, Folder 52-53)
    - 03-03: Matos Interiors, 2003; 47228 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - 03-04: Pinney, Payne Interior Study, 2003; 47227 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - 03-05: South Gate Condominium, Railing/Deck, 2003; 47226 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - 04-01: "Plasma" Renovations, 2003-2004; 47225 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - 04-01: (99-29) Club 2000, 1999-2000; 47224 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - 04-02: 432 Main Street Addition, 2004; 47223 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - 04-03: Kia Showroom, 2003-2004; 47222 (Box 14, Folder 60-61)
    - 04-04: Zoto's Driveway, 2004; 47221 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - 04-05: Buzaid Garage Renovation, 2003-2004; 47220 (Box 14, Folder 63-64)
    - 04-05: Starbuck's, 2004; 47219 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - 04-06: Danbury Ambulance, 2004; 47218 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Series 2: Specifications/Contracts/Project Manuals, 47146
  - 76-06 - 87-19, 49845
    - 76-06: The United Methodist Church Addition, New Milford, CT (Specifications), 1977; 47216 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 78-? J. S. Boots Family Residence, Darien, CT (Specifications), 1978; 47215 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 78-12: Hubbard's Cubbard (Outline Specifications), 1979; 47214 (Box 15, Folder 3-4)
    - 79-11: The Hull Building Renovations (Outline Specifications), 1982; 47213 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 80-10: Godfrey Apartments (Specifications), 1980-1981; 47212 (Box 15, Folder 6-9)
    - 81-02: Wooster School, Arnold House Addition (Outline Specifications), June 1981, 47211 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - 81-02: Wooster School Maintenance and Repair Survey, Buildings 1-27 (incl. photos & drawing prints), 1981; 47210 (Box 18, Folder 24-34)
    - 82-18: The Hull Building (Outline Specifications), 1982; 47209 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - 82-32: Zotos Apartments (Specifications), 1982; 47208 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - 82-43: Vincent Apartments (Outline Specs), 1984; 47207 (Box 15, Folder 13-15)
    - 83-01: Bear Mountain Ranger Residence (Contract and Specifications), 1983; 47206 (Box 15, Folder 16-18)
    - 84-02: Old Library Interior (Contract & Specifications), 1984; 47205 (Box 15, Folder 19-21)
    - 84-02: Old Library Interior, Office Copy (Contract and Specifications), 1984; 47204 (Box 15, Folder 22-23)
    - 84-11: IBM, Seven Penn Center, Philadelphia, PA (Specifications), 1984; 47203 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - 85-05: IBM Commerce Plaza, Hartford, CT (Specifications), 1986; 47202 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - 85-09: Halpin Court, Project Manual, 1991; 47201 (Box 15, Folder 26-28)
    - 85-20: Northside Animal Hospital (Specifications), 1986; 47200 (Box 15, Folder 29-30)
    - 85-20: Northside Animal Hospital, Office Copy (Specs), 1986; 47199 (Box 15, Folder 31-32)
    - 85-31: Nolan Enterprises Offices (Specifications), 1986; 47198 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - 86-03: Old Library Windows (Contract Documents), 1986; 47197 (Box 15, Folder 34-36)
    - 86-03: Old Library Windows, Office Copy (Contract Docs), 1986; 47196 (Box 15, Folder 37-38)
    - 86-13: IBM - 101 Merritt Seven Corporate Park (Specs), 1986; 47195 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - 86-24: Old Library Elevator (Contract & Specs), 1986-1987; 47194 (Box 15, Folder 40-42)
    - 86-32: Sandpit Condominium Project (Specifications), 1989; 47193 (Box 15, Folder 43-50)
    - 87-19: The Second Meting House VFW Building, Phase 1 (Specifications), 1988; 47192 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - 87-23: Ericson Reconstruction, 47187
    - Project Manual, 1987; 47191 (Box 15, Folder 52-54)
    - Model, Ericson House proposed design (3 Pandanaram Rd), 1990s; 47190 (Item Model_1)
    - Ericson Letters/Agreements/Zoning Reg./Bids, 1989-1991; 47189 (Box 18, Folder 35-38)
    - Original Certificate (14x15) from the National Society of the Daughters of the American Revolution awarded to Grace Penny Ericson on 21 May 1932., 47188 (Box 29, Folder *)
  - 88-09 - 03-05, 49846
    - 88-09: IBM Corporation, Springfield, MA (Specifications), 1988; 47186 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 89-09: Delucia Apartments, Project Manual (office copy), 1989; 47185 (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
    - 89-11: Ives House Restoration, Project Manual (office copy), 1991; 47184 (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
    - 90-09: Supercuts, Architectural Design Manual, 1990; 47183 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 90-24: One Hamden Center, Interior Alterations (office copy), 1991; 47182 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - 91-02: Liberty Terrace Condominiums (Outline Specs), 1992; 47181 (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
    - 91-03: Union Savings Galleria (Const. Cost Est.), 1991-1994; 47180 (Box 16, Folder 9a-b)
    - 91-03: Union Savings Galleria (Specifications), 1992; 47179 (Box 16, Folder 10-21)
    - 91-03: Union Savings Galleria, Project Manual, 1990-1994; 47178 (Box 16, Folder 22-28)
    - 91-07: 100 Elm Street Addition, Project Manual, 1991-1992; 47177 (Box 16, Folder 29-31)
    - 91-09: Dunkin' Donuts (Specifications), 1990-1991; 47176 (Box 16, Folder 32-34)
    - 93-01: Bishop Curtis Homes of Danbury, Project Manual, 1993; 47175 (Box 16, Folder 35-40)
    - 93-02 Pernick Library, Molding ID/Specs., 1993; 47174 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - 93-11: Alligator Alley, Mechanical & Electrical Specifications (office copy), 1993; 47173 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - 93-15: Savings Bank of Danbury Addition, Project Manual, 1994-1995; 47172 (Box 16, Folder 43-48)
    - 93-15: Savings Bank of Danbury Addition, Project Manual (office copy), 1995; 47171 (Box 16, Folder 49-56)
    - 93-15: Model, Savings Bank Loan Center, undated; 47170 (Item Model_2)
    - 93-15B: Savings Bank of Danbury Addition, "Drive Up" Transaction Window (office copy), 1994; 47169 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - 94-04: 100 Danbury Road Building B, Mechanical & Electrical Specifications, 1994; 47168 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - 94-14: Sperry Rail Service, Specification Cuts Compilation, 1994; 47167 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - 95-04: Wilton Ridge Homes, Project Manual, 1995; 47166 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - 96-16: Danbury Bowling Center, Outline Specifications, 1997; 47165 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - 97-01: Saving Bank of Danbury Restoration, Proj. Manual, 1997; 47164 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - 97-08: Savings Bank Loan Center (Specifications), 1997; 47163 (Box 17, Folder 7-9)
    - 97-11: Tarrywile Park Lavatories, Outline Specifications, 1997; 47162 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - 97-14: Datahr Rehabilitation Institute, Outline Specs, 1997; 47161 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - 97-17: Palace View Senior Housing (Specifications), 1997; 47160 (Box 17, Folder 12-14)
    - 97-19: Danbury Community Health Center and Senior Meeting Hall (Specifications), 1997-1998; 47159 (Box 17, Folder 15-17)
    - 97-19: Danbury Community Health Center and Senior Meeting Hall, Program Manual, 1998; 47158 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - 97-19: Danbury Community Health Center and Senior Meeting Hall, Outline Specifications, 1998; 47157 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - 97-19: Danbury Community Health Center and Senior Meeting Hall (Specifications), 1997-1998; 47156 (Box 17, Folder 20-23)
    - 98-11: Saving Bank Loan Center (Specifications), 1997-1998; 47155 (Box 17, Folder 24-28)
    - 99-07: United Way of Northern Fairfield County Renovations, Outline Specifications (office copy), 1997; 47154 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - 20-32: Augustana Homes, Inc. DBA Bishop Curtis Homes, Architectural Specifications, 2000; 47153 (Box 17, Folder 30-32)
    - 20-45: Paulo's Auto Repair Shop, Outline Specifications, 2002; 47152 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - 02-02: Danbury Senior Center of the City of Danbury, 2002; 47151 (Box 17, Folder 34-43)
    - 02-02: Danbury Senior Center of the City of Danbury, Contract & Specifications, 2002-2003; 47150 (Box 17, Folder 44-51)
    - 02-02: New Senior Citizen Center, Geotechnical Engineering Report, 2002; 47149 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - 02-05: Blackstone Industries, Phase I, Outline Specifications/Bids, 2002; 47148 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - 03-05: South Gate Condominiums Plaza Repairs & New Railings, Outline Specifications, 2002-2003; 47147 (Box 17, Folder 54)
- Series 3: Blueprints and Drawings, 47144
  - Blueprints and Drawings, undated; 47145 (Box OS Drawing Boxes 1-9, Folder *)
  - Blueprints and Drawings, undated (Box 10-11)
- Series 4: Request for Qualifications & Bids, 47123
  - 2004: Senior Center, Phase II Expansion, 47143 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 2004: St. John Church fire Rebuild, 47142 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 2001: The Ryder House Bid Packet, 47141 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 1997: Savings Bank of Danbury Loan Center, 47140 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 1993: Danbury Public Library Renovations, 47139 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 1993: 40 Units/Elderly Housing, Redding, 47138 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - 1993: New Milford Children Center, 47137 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - 1992: Union Station Restoration, 47136 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - 1992: Waterford Housing Authority, 47135 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - 1991: Hart Bus Transfer Facility, 47134 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - 1990: Main Street and Redevelopment Area Improvements, 47133 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - 1990: Danbury Downtown Improvement Plan, 47132 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - 1990: Danbury Downtown Improvement Plan, 47131 (Item Map folder *, Folder *)
    2009 Accretion. 20+ft plans for sidewalk construction along Main St. Not implemented. Shows business names and building outlines of Main St. ~from White St. to Keeler St.
  - 1990: DOT/Teen Center, 47130 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - 1990: The Cromwell Animal Shelter, 47129 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - 1989: Black Rock Lighthouse, 47128 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - 1989: Downtown Improvement Plan, Streetscape and Public Parking Lots, 47127 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - 1989: General Government Space Needs, 47126 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - 1984: Danbury Downtown Revitalization Bid, The Nolan Enterprises Redevelopment Team (includes DVD Presentation, and Request for Proposals by the City of Danbury, 47125 (Box 18, Folder 39-49)
  - Danbury Downtown Revitalization Plan, 1984; 47124 (Item Map folder *, Folder *)
    2009 Accretion. 1 Plan showing the confluence of Main, Liberty and Patriot Streets.
- Series 5: Photographs & Slides, 46736
  - Photographs mounted on matt boards (various sizes), 47106
    - 1958 College Thesis (photostats), 47122 (Box OS 3, Folder 1)
    - 1965 Projects w/John Graham Office, NYC, 47121 (Box OS 3, Folder 1)
    - 1968 First Zurlo Office/Residence, 47120 (Box OS 3, Folder 2)
    - 1968 First Congregational Chapel, New Milford, 47119 (Box OS 3, Folder 2)
    - 1969-70 John Horton House and Johnson Residence w/Eliot Noyes, 1969-1970; 47118 (Box OS 3, Folder 3)
    - 1971 Meadow Street Fire Station w/Eliot Noyes, 47117 (Box OS 3, Folder 3)
    - 1972 Venture "8" Greenwich, 47116 (Box OS 3, Folder 4)
    - 1972 Fladerman Kitchen, New Milford, 47115 (Box OS 3, Folder 4)
    - 1973 Barlas Addition, Lake Waubeeka, 47114 (Box OS 3, Folder 5)
    - 1975 Murphy Residence (2), 47113 (Box OS 3, Folder 6)
    - 1975 New Hope Baptist Church, 47112 (Box OS 3, Folder 5)
    - 1976 Ryder Residence, Lake Waubeeka, 47111 (Box OS 3, Folder 7)
    - 1978 United Methodist Church, 47110 (Box OS 3, Folder 7)
    - 1978 Hubbard's Cubbard, 47109 (Box OS 3, Folder 8)
    - 1979 Martins's Mens Store, 47108 (Box OS 3, Folder 8)
    - 1979 Barry Law Offices (2), 47107 (Box OS 3, Folder 9)
  - Photographs (enclosed in plastic frames), 11x14, 47083
    - 1981 Hull Building Renovation, Main Street, 47105 (Box 19, Item 1)
    - 1981 Hull Building addition, Liberty Street, 47104 (Box 19, Item 2)
    - 1983 Bear Mountain Range Residence, 47103 (Box 19, Item 3)
    - 1983 The Vincent Apartments, Crosby Street, 47102 (Box 19, Item 4)
    - 1984 DeVoe Insurance Renovation, Main Street, 47101 (Box 19, Item 5)
    - 1984 Music Guild Restoration, Main Street, 47100 (Box 19, Item 6)
    - 1986 Northside Animal Hospital, Pandanaram Road, 47099 (Box 20, Item 1)
    - 1986 Sandpit (luxury) Condominiums, Germantown (2), 47098 (Box 20, Item 2)
    - 1986 Old Library Restoration & Addition, 47097 (Box 20, Item 3)
    - 1987 Bigelow Condominiums, South Street, 47096 (Box 20, Item 4)
    - 1987 Brushy Hill Renovation (Brushy Ridge), 47095 (Box 20, Item 5)
    - 1987 Leli (office/retail) Building, Fire Rebuild, Main Street, 47094 (Box 20, Item 6)
    - 1988 Hatter's Yard (affordable) Condos, Franklin Street, 47093 (Box 20, Item 7)
    - 1989 Brookview Office/Restaurant Complex, New Milford, 47092 (Box 20, Item 8)
    - 1990 Ericson House Reconstruction (not built), 47091 (Box 21, Item 1)
    - 1994 Liberty Terrace Condominiums (10x14 glass framed) 1995 Bishop Curtis (elderly) Homes & Addition, Main St., 47090 (Box 21, Item 2)
    - 1998 Palace View (elderly) Apartments, Main Street, 47089 (Box 21, Item 3)
    - 1998 Community Health Center, 47088 (Box 21, Item 4)
    - 1999 Savings Bank of Danbury, West Street, 47087 (Box 21, Item 5)
    - 2003 Senior Center (Elmwood Hall), Elmwood Place, 47086 (Box 21, Item 6)
    - 1983 Phineas Park Apartments, Bethel, 47085 (Box OS 4, Folder *)
    - 1984 Downtown Redevelopment Proposal, 8 acres (2), 47084 (Box OS 5, Folder *)
  - Photographs (professionally mounted/frameless) 30x40, 47076
    - 1978-1994: 12-8x10 Before/After photographs, (4) by Gilles Rousseau Studio., 47082 (Item Map folder *, Folder *)
    - 1987 Sandpit (luxury) Condominiums (Model), 47081 (Item Map folder *, Folder *)
    - 1987 Hatter's Yard (affordable) Condominiums, 47080 (Item Map folder *, Folder *)